worldventures.biz 2014-02-07

# Privacy Policy

Privacy Policy
Last modified: April 6, 2013
Introduction
WorldVentures Marketing LLC ("Company" or "We") respect your privacy and are committed to protecting it through our
compliance with this policy.
This policy and any other documents referred to in it describes the personal information that we collect from you, or that
you provide on this website www.worldventures.biz (our "Website") (which may link to other WorldVentures websites) and
how that information may be used or disclosed by us.
This Privacy Policy relates to information we collect on this website, in email, text and other electronic messages between
you and this Website and us, through mobile and desktop applications you download from this Website, which provide
dedicated non-browser-based interaction between you and this Website and when you interact with our advertising and
applications on third-party websites and services, if those applications or advertising include links to this policy.
Other WorldVentures websites may contain privacy policies which are different from this Privacy Policy. In addition,
specific terms and conditions may apply to specific content, services or products contained in or available from such other
WorldVentures websites. In the event such additional or specific terms are inconsistent with the terms contained in this
Privacy Policy, the additional or specific terms shall prevail. On your visits to WorldVentures websites please check the
privacy policy of each website which you visit and do not assume that this privacy policy applies to all WorldVentures
websites.
This policy does not apply to information collected on any third-party site or by any third-party application that may link to
or be accessible from the Website, unless such third party site or third party application includes links to this policy.
Please read the following carefully to understand our policies and practices regarding your personal information and how
we will treat it. If you do not agree with our policies and practices, your choice is not to use our Website. By using or
accessing our Website, you agree to this privacy policy. This policy may change from time to time and your continued use
of the Website is deemed to be acceptance of such changes, so please check the policy periodically for updates.
Children Under the Age of 18
Our Website is not intended for children under 18 years of age. No one under age 18 may provide any personal
information to or on the Website. We do not knowingly collect personal information from children under 18. If you are
under 18, please do not register on the Website, make any purchases through the Website or send any information about
yourself to us, including your name, address, telephone number or email address. In the event that we learn that we have
collected personal information from a child under age 18 without verification of parental consent, we will delete that
information. If you believe that we might have any information from or about a child under 18, please contact us at
privacy@worldventures.com.
Information We Collect About You and How We Collect It
We collect several types of information from and about users of our Website, including:
         •         Information you provide to us.
         •         Information we collect as you navigate through the site, including usage details, IP addresses.
         •         Information we receive from third parties, for example, our business partners and independent sales
                   representatives.
         •         Information about your internet connection, the equipment you use to access our Website and usage
                   details.
         We collect this information:
         •         Directly from you when you provide it to us.

       •       Automatically as you navigate through the site. Information collected automatically may include usage
               details, IP addresses and information collected through cookies, web beacons and other tracking
               technologies.
       •       From third parties, for example, our business partners.
Information You Provide to Us
We may collect and use the following information that you provide to us:
       •       Information that you provide by filling in forms on our Website. This includes information provided at the
               time of registering to use our Website, subscribing to our services, posting material or requesting further
               services. We may also ask you for information when you enter a contest or promotion sponsored by us,
               and when you report a problem with our Website.
       •       Records and copies of your correspondence (including email addresses), if you contact us.
       •       Your responses to surveys that we might ask you to complete for research purposes, although you do not
               have to respond to them.
       •       Details of transactions you carry out through our Website and of the fulfilment of your orders. You may be
               required to provide financial information before placing an order through our Website.
       •       Your search queries on the Website.
Usage Details, IP Addresses, Cookies and Other Technologies
       •       Usage Details and IP Addresses. As you navigate through the Website, we may also collect details of
               your visits to our Website, including, but not limited to, traffic data, location data, logs and other
               communication data, whether this is required for our own billing purposes or otherwise and the resources
               that you access, as well as information about your computer and Internet connection, including your IP
               address, operating system and browser type, for system administration and to report aggregate
               information to our advertisers. This is statistical data about our users' equipment, browsing actions and
               patterns, and does not identify any individual.
       •       Cookies. For the same reason, we may obtain information about your general Internet usage by using
               cookies. A cookie is a small file stored on the hard drive of your computer. Use of cookies help us to
               improve our Website and to deliver a better and more personalized service by enabling us to:
               •         Estimate our audience size and usage patterns.
               •         Store information about your preferences, allowing us to customize our Website according to your
                         individual interests.
               •         Speed up your searches.
               •         Recognize you when you return to our Website.
               You may refuse to accept cookies by activating the appropriate setting on your browser. However, if you
               select this setting you may be unable to access certain parts of our Website. Unless you have adjusted
               your browser setting so that it will refuse cookies, our system will issue cookies when you direct your
               browser to our Website.
       •       Web Beacons. Pages of the Website may contain electronic images known as web beacons (also
               referred to as single-pixel gifs) that permit the Company to count users who have visited those pages and
               for other related website statistics (for example, recording the popularity of certain website content and
               verifying system and server integrity). Web beacons are not used to access your personal information on
               the Website and are only used to compile aggregated statistics concerning use of the Website.
                                                               2

          •       Third-Party Advertiser Use of Cookies and Other Tracking Technologies. Some advertisements on
                  the Website are served by third-party advertising companies. Please note that our advertisers may also
                  use cookies alone or in conjunction with web beacons or other tracking technologies to collect information
                  about our users. We do not have control over third-party advertisers' cookies or how they may be used. If
                  you have any questions about an advertisement, you should contact the responsible advertiser directly.
User Contributions
You are responsible for any content, including personal information, that you contribute to be published or displayed
(hereinafter, "posted") on the Website, or transmit to other users of the Website (collectively, "User Contributions").
Your User Contributions are posted on and transmitted to other users of the Website at your own risk. Please be aware
that no security measures are perfect or impenetrable. Additionally, we cannot control the actions of other users of the
Website with whom you may choose to share your User Contributions. Therefore, we cannot and do not guarantee that
your User Contributions will not be viewed by unauthorized persons. We are not responsible for circumvention of any
privacy settings or security measures contained on the Website. You understand and acknowledge that, even after
removal, copies of your User Contributions may remain viewable in cached and archived pages, or might have been
copied or stored by other Website users.
Uses Made of the Information
We use information that we collect about you or that you provide to us, including any personal information, in the following
ways:
          •       To present our Website and its contents in a suitable and effective manner for you and for your computer.
          •       To provide you with information, products or services that you request from us.
          •       To carry out our obligations and enforce our rights arising from any contracts entered into between you
                  and us.
          •       To notify you about changes to our service.
          •       To allow you to participate in interactive features of our service, when you choose to do so.
          •       In any other way we may describe when you provide the information.
          •       For any other purpose with your consent.
We may also use your information, or permit selected third parties to use your information, to contact you about goods
and services that may be of interest to you where you have consented to be contacted for such purposes. If you do not
want us to use your information in this way, or to provide your information to third parties for marketing purposes, please
send us an email with the subject line “unsubscribe” to privacy@worldventures.com
We do not disclose your personally identifiable information to our advertisers, but we may provide them with aggregated
information about our users (for example, we may report to them that 500 men aged under 30 clicked on their
advertisement on a given day). We may also use such aggregated information to help advertisers reach the kind of
audience they want to target. We may make use of the personal information we have collected from you to enable us to
comply with our advertisers' wishes by displaying their advertisement to that target audience. Even though we only
disclose aggregate information that is not personally-identifiable to advertisers without your consent, when you click on or
otherwise interact with an advertisement there is a possibility that the advertiser may assume that you meet the target
criteria they selected.
Disclosure of Your Information
We may disclose personal information that you provide via this Website to the following third parties:
          •       Our holding entities, subsidiaries and affiliates.
          •       Contractors including WorldVentures Independent Sales Representatives and service providers we use to
                  support our business.
                                                                 3

         •        To a buyer in the event of a merger, divestiture, restructuring, reorganization, dissolution or any other
                  form of sale of some or all of WorldVentures Marketing LLC’s assets or those of its holding company or
                  entity, whether as a going concern or as part of bankruptcy, liquidation or similar proceeding, in which
                  personal information held by WorldVentures Marketing LLC about its customers is among the assets
                  transferred.
         •        To third parties to market their products or services to you if you have not opted out of these disclosures.
                  We contractually require these third parties to keep personal information confidential and use it only for
                  the purposes for which we disclose it to them.
         •        To fulfill the purpose for which you provide it.
         •        For any other purpose disclosed by us when you provide the information.
         •        With your consent
We may also disclose your personal information to third parties to:
         •        Comply with any court order or other legal obligation.
         •        If we believe disclosure is necessary or appropriate to protect the rights, property, or safety of
                  WorldVentures Marketing LLC, our customers, or others. This includes exchanging information with other
                  companies and organizations for the purposes of fraud protection and credit risk reduction.
Choices About How We Use and Disclose Your Information
We strive to provide you with choices regarding the personal information you provide to us. We have created mechanisms
to provide you with the following control over your information:
         •        Cookies. If you do not wish us to collect cookies, you may set your browser to refuse cookies, or to alert
                  you when cookies are being sent. If you do so, please note that some parts of this site may then be
                  inaccessible or not function properly.
         •        Promotional Offers from Third Parties. If you do not wish us to share your personal information with
                  unaffiliated or non-agent third parties for promotional purposes, you can opt-out by sending an email with
                  the subject line “unsubscribe” to privacy@worldventures.com.
         •        Promotional Offers from the Company. If you do not wish to have your email address used for
                  promotional purposes by the Company, you can opt-out by sending an email with the subject line
                  “unsubscribe” to privacy@worldventures.com. You can also always opt-out of receiving email information
                  from us other than the email informing you of the completion of user registration, correction of user data,
                  change of password or change of applicable terms and conditions by sending us an email stating your
                  request at privacy@worldventures.com. If we have sent you a promotional email, you may send us an
                  email at privacy@worldventures.com asking to be omitted from future email distributions. This opt out
                  does not apply to information provided to the Company as a result of a product or service purchase,
                  product service experience or other transactions.
         •        Personalized Advertising. If you do not want us to use personal information that we gather to allow third
                  parties to personalize advertisements we display to you, you can opt-out by sending an email with the
                  subject line “unsubscribe” to privacy@worldventures.com
We do not control third parties' collection or use of your information to serve interest-based advertising. However these
third parties may provide you with ways to choose not to have your information collected or used in this way. You can opt
out of receiving targeted ads from members of the Network Advertising Initiative ("NAI") on the NAI's website.
You should review this privacy policy carefully, because if you do not agree with our practices, your ultimate choice is not
to use the Website. Remember, by using any part of the Website, you accept and agree to our privacy practices. If we
update this privacy policy, your continued use of the Website (following the posting of the revised privacy policy) means
that you accept and agree to the terms of the revised privacy policy.
Accessing and Correcting Your Personal Information
                                                                 4

If you have provided personal information when registering to receive services or information, you can review and update
your personal information by logging into the Website and visiting your account profile page and making changes with the
exception of your name, Social Security Number (SSN) or Tax Identification Number. To change the name, Social
Security Number, or Tax Identification Number on an account, the account holder must telephone us at Customer
Services. If you have forgotten your password, once you have tried to register and failed, you can click on the "Forgot your
password?" link to reach a page on which you can submit your email address. Your user name and password then will be
emailed to you.
You may also send us an email at privacy@worldventures.com to request access to, correct or delete any personal
information that you have provided to us. We cannot delete your personal information except by also deleting your user
account.
Your California Privacy Rights
California Civil Code Section § 1798.83 permits users of our Website that are California residents to request certain
information regarding our disclosure of personal information to third parties for their direct marketing purposes. To make
such a request, please send an email to privacy@worldventures.com or write us at: 5360 legacy Drive Building 1 Suite
300, Plano, Texas 75024.
Data Security
We have implemented measures designed to secure your personal information from accidental loss and from
unauthorized access, use, alteration and disclosure. All information you provide to us is stored on our secure servers
behind firewalls. Any payment transactions and personally identifiable information will be encrypted using SSL technology.
The safety and security of your information also depends on you. Where we have given you (or where you have chosen) a
password for access to certain parts of our Website, you are responsible for keeping this password confidential. We ask
you not to share your password with anyone. We urge you to be careful about giving out information in public areas of the
Website like message boards. The information you share in public areas may be viewed by any user of the Website.
Unfortunately, the transmission of information via the Internet is not completely secure. Although we do our best to protect
your personal information, we cannot guarantee the security of your personal information transmitted to our Website. Any
transmission of personal information is at your own risk.
Changes to Our Privacy Policy
It is our policy to post any changes we make to our Privacy Policy on this page and the Website home page. If we make
material changes to this Privacy Policy, we will notify you by email or through a notice on the Website home page. The
date the Privacy Policy was last revised is identified at the top of the page.
Contact Information
To ask questions or comment             about     this   privacy   policy   and our   privacy   practices,  contact  us   at
privacy@worldventures.com.
                                                                5
